https://www.facilitiesnet.com/privacy.asp

Discover 18 Key Products & Services For Facility Professionals »
Product & Technology Innovations »
Check out the 2020 Vision Award Winners »
Daily eNews - Sign Up
Try fnPrime™ Today! »
fnPrime™ is our new member community. Each month, new resources will be available to help facility professionals advance their careers, save their organizations money, and tackle key trends facing the industry. See what's in it for you.
Six Climate And Resilience Strategies You Can Do Right Now »
Facility Management Lessons Learned During The Pandemic »
View All »
Featured
Branded FeaturesDive deep into FM topics from Top Manufacturers
Building Types
Critical Facilities
Data Centers
Education
Health Care
Government
Commercial Office
Management Topics
Trending
COVID-19 »
School District Implements IAQ and Coronavirus Safety Measures for Reopening »
How the Pandemic is Changing Healthcare Design »
4 Air Quality Technologies Can Mitigate Coronavirus Spread »
Jobs
Job Board
Post Your Jobs
Products
Product Press Releases Updates and releases of facilities products from top manufacturerss
Press Releases By Company
Case Studies Analysis and demonstration of products and services for the benefit of commercial and institutional facilities
2020 Vision Award Winners
Product & Technology Innovations eBook
Discover 18 Key Products & Services For Facility Professionals
Managing Buildings
ADA
Commercial Office Facilities
Data Centers
Design & Construction
Educational Facilities
Emergency Preparedness
Energy Efficiency
ProFM Credential
Use a Smart Building Implementation Model to Transform the Built Environment
Part of the Facilities Technology Summit
December 15, 2020
10 AM to 2:30 PM See Agenda »Smarter Buildings: Practical Steps for FMs
Part of the Facilities Technology Summit
December 15, 2020
10 AM to 2:30 PM See Agenda »Water - The Invisible Safety Hazard
December 17, 202011 AM ET Register Today »
Magazines
Building Operating Management
Read Current Issue
Archives
Digital Subscription
Print Subscription
Facebook
@bldgopmgmt
search
Go to fnPrime »
Six Climate And Resilience Strategies You Can Do Right Now »
Facility Management Lessons Learned During The Pandemic »
FEATURED
Branded Features »
FACILITY TYPE
Data Centers
Education
Health Care
Government
Commercial Office
MANAGEMENT TOPICS
ADA
TRENDING
COVID-19 »
School District Implements IAQ and Coronavirus Safety Measures for Reopening »
How the Pandemic is Changing Healthcare Design »
4 Air Quality Technologies Can Mitigate Coronavirus Spread »
JOBS
Job Listings & Salary Information
Post A Job
PRODUCTS
Building Product Releases
Case Studies
2020 Vision Award Winners
Product & Technology Innovations eBook
Discover 18 Key Products & Services For Facility Professionals
Press Releases
Press Releases By Company
EDUCATION
UPCOMING
Use a Smart Building Implementation Model to Transform the Built Environment
Part of the Facilities Technology Summit
December 15, 2020
10 AM to 2:30 PM See Agenda »Smarter Buildings: Practical Steps for FMs
Part of the Facilities Technology Summit
December 15, 2020
10 AM to 2:30 PM See Agenda »Water - The Invisible Safety Hazard
December 17, 202011 AM ET Register Today »
Free Webcasts
Democasts
Premium Webinars
Educational Resources
ProFM Credential
MAGAZINES
Building Operating Management
Facility Maintenance Decisions
FacilitiesNet Policies
This website is a property of Trade Press Media Group.
Policies for all our websites, eNewsletters, email marketing and other digital interactions are contained herein.
Trade Press Media Group Privacy and Cookie Policy
This privacy statement is to demonstrate our commitment to full disclosure of the information collection and use practices applicable to this website and our digital products. This privacy statement discloses what information we collect via this website, our email, eNewsletters and other digital touchpoints and how we use it.
The Purposes For Collecting and Using Your Information
To provide our users with news, education, information and content and to connect our users with exhibitors, advertisers or sponsors when users are interested in their products or services.
What We Collect
In general, you may visit this website without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.
Personal Information: name, job title, company, physical mailing address, e-mail address, and telephone number, association affiliations, content and product interests, job responsibilities, purchasing intentions, digital behaviors
Financial Information: if applicable, financial information such as your credit card information
When you browse our websites or use our emails, we collect the IP address of your computer, your device information and click data (information that site users generate as they move from page to page and click on items) and this data is aggregated with usage data from all users. We also collect the type of information you engage with and your actions to provide you with more pertinent advertising messages and enhance our products to better serve our audience.
Some of our email, website, webcast, trade show/conferences, print and other products require you to give us personally-identifiable information. If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys or contest entries, any information provided in such communications may be collected as Personal Information.
Information on Children
As a business-to-business company, we do not knowingly collect information from children. On-line registration and website usage is restricted to adults who are professionally engaged in the businesses we serve.
How Your Data Will Be Used and What It Will Be Used For?
Financial Information
If you submit Financial Information, we only use that information to verify your credit and collect payments for your purchases, orders, registrations, etc. We do not keep or store your credit card information after the purchase.
Personal Information
If you elect to provide us Personal Information, we use it primarily to deliver the service you requested.
Used to mail you print subscriptions or mail you trade show/conference and educational event updates;
Used to contact you about your subscriptions, registrations or attendance at our events;
Used to market trade shows, education, certifications, products and services to you, to get more relevant marketing in front of you, to enhance our products by better understanding how you react or engage with our products;
Used in aggregate to communicate to our sponsors or advertisers about the nature of the audience they would be marketing to;
Used for our email list rental/email list marketing;
Used for third-party reporting to help our customers know who they are advertising to, who has engaged with their advertising and who should be contacted for followup.
Some Trade Press Media products are designed to connect you with a third party or help you get relevant third-party marketing related to actions you have taken.
For those products we may share your Personal Information with the third-party to make that happen.
If you register for a webcast we share your personal information, including email, with our sponsors represented in the webcast so they can follow up with you after the event.
If you click on certain email links we may share your personal information, including email with the represented advertiser(s) so they can follow up with you related to the interest you indicated by clicking.
If you filled out a website form we may share your personal information, including email with the represented advertiser(s) so they can follow up with you related to the interest you indicated by submitting the form.
If you registered for a trade show or conference we may share your personal information with exhibitors or sponsors to help them determine if our event provides them with a relevant audience and so they can follow up with you after the event.
If you had an exhibitor scan your badge at one of our events we may share your personal information, including email with the exhibitor so they can follow up with you after the event
Information Sharing
We share your Personal Information with Trade Press Media Group affiliates and partners and third parties. We rent lists compiled from the Personal Information (including e-mail addresses) gathered from this website, our print publications,
trade shows/events or other products we offer.
Except as otherwise provided in this privacy policy, we will keep your Personal Information and your Financial Information private and will not share it with third parties. However, we reserve the right to release information about visitors, including Personal Information and Financial Information, when release is required to comply with the law, to enforce our Terms of Service, or to protect the rights, property or safety of this website, the public or Trade Press Media Group. On certain Trade Press Media Group websites, when you register for Educational Webinars/Continuing Education, we collect personally-identifiable information from you. This information is required to be collected by, and is shared with, the relevant accreditation bodies. Our Editorial, Education and Customer Support Staff also have access to this information, including evaluation forms and participant information. This information is used in assessing educational needs and in planning marketing activities. Some Trade Press Media products are designed to connect you with a third party or help you get relevant third-party marketing related to actions you have taken. For those products we may share your Personal Information with the third-party to make that happen. We reserve the right to use this information as otherwise permitted in this Privacy Policy.
Aggregated information
We sometimes provide aggregated usage or tracking information collected from this website to third parties.
Third Party and Affiliated Links
Our websites contain links to external websites including suppliers, advertisers and affiliates. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the content of, or information gathered by, these other websites. We do not endorse any of these websites or the products or services associated with such websites merely because they are linked to our website.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a string of data sent by a website to a user that is inserted in a file of the web browser of the user visiting the site. Trade Press Media Group uses temporary, session-specific cookies to ensure visits to its website are smooth and customized for the visitor. Such cookies allow us to provide a visitor's browser with information tailored to the visitor's preferences and needs. Trade Press Media Group also uses permanent or persistent cookies that remain on a visitor's computer after the visitor leaves a Trade Press Media Group website.
If you do not want your browser to accept cookies, you can turn off the cookie acceptance option in the browser's settings. However, disabling the cookie support function of the browser will prevent our website from functioning properly and you may not be able to use fully all of the site's features and information and will in most cases be forced to re-register every time you visit the site.
We use advertising companies to develop banner ads for our website. These ads may contain cookies. These companies collect cookies sent to your browser through the banner ads and we do not have control of, or access to, this data.
We also use Google Analytics, Facebook and additional third-party remarketing code. This allows us to stay engaged with our target audience who have previously visited our website and show you relevant ads across the web or when you search on Google.
Security and Encryption
This website takes commercially reasonable precautions to protect your information. We use SSL encryption technology on the portions of our website that accept Financial Information and we use a secure server to encrypt Financial Information transmitted between your browser and our server. As a result, data you submit to our website, such as credit card and payment information, is transmitted securely over the Internet.
How you can Control Your Information
Visitors to this website can decide whether they want to receive targeted promotional information from Trade Press Media Group. On the email management page, visitors can choose to request Trade Press Media Group not to e-mail them. Should visitors accept promotional email from Trade Press Media Group, any email they receive will include instructions on how to be removed from any or all of Trade Press Media Group's promotional email lists.
Users can also contact us via email at: notify@tradepress.com or call us at 414-228-7701 and ask us to stop emailing them or have their information removed from our database.
Your California Privacy Rights
California's "Shine the Light" law, Cal. Civ. Code 1798.83, permits our users who are residents of California to request and obtain from us, once per year, free of charge, information about the Personal Information and Financial Information, if any, that we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information includes a listing of the categories of personal information that was shared, and the names and addresses of the third parties with whom we shared the information.
If you are a California resident, and would like to make such a request, please submit your request, in writing, to:
Digital Privacy Manager
Trade Press Media Group
2100 W. Florist Ave.
Glendale, WI 53209
Exceptions
Trade Press Media Group may buy or sell various assets. In the event that we sell some or all of our assets, or our site is acquired by another company, information about our visitors, including Personal Information and Financial Information, may be among the transferred assets.
Whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by third parties online - for example in chat rooms or on message boards - Trade Press Media Group has no ability or obligation to prevent third-party access to such information and Trade Press Media Group undertakes no responsibility to keep such information private.
Notification of Changes
Trade Press Media Group reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this privacy policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on the website. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the website.
Non-discrimination
Trade Press Media Group, Inc. is committed to providing an educational opportunity for all persons and admits participants of any race, color, gender, sexual preference, age, non-disqualifying handicap, religion or creed, or national or ethnic origin.
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
Event & Tradeshow Policies:
General Policies
No one under 18 is allowed in the sessions, expo hall or receptions.
Registration and access to NFMT is exclusively for qualified end-users. End-users are defined as individuals responsible for specifying or buying the products and/or services of exhibiting companies. Non Buyers are those that sell products, services, integration or consulting for the facility management industry. If you represent a company or supplier that provides products or services, you will be registered as a Non Buyer and a fee of $395 will be applicable. Registering as a non buyer, you acknowledge and understand that you are liable for any and all damages resulting from any and all attempts to solicit the Exhibitors or Attendees participating in NFMT. Individuals wishing to use this event to solicit exhibitors or attendees will be charged a cost of $3,600 per contact or solicitation. All registrations will be vetted and canceled if found to be in noncompliance with this policy.
Badges must be worn at all times.
Photography or video production of exhibitors' booth and products displayed therein without verbal authorization from the exhibitor is strictly prohibited.
By attending, you consent to the use of your image by Show Management and their partners without charge or obligation.
Briefcases, toolboxes, boxes and bags are subject to inspection.
Soliciting by non-exhibitors at the event is prohibited (Suit-casing Policy)
Your Acceptance of these Terms
By using our website, products or services, you signify your acceptance of the terms of the Trade Press Media Group Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of the Trade Press Media Group Privacy Policy, please do not use the website, products and/or services and exit the site immediately.
Revised May 27, 2020
Contact Information:
Digital Privacy Manager
Trade Press Media Group
2100 W. Florist Ave.
Glendale, WI 53209
414-228-7701
notify@tradepress.com
